Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Wait.
Why?
Not feeling up to it anymore?
Well…
I give you 5 seconds.
(Every decision has its binary choices.)
(Which choice should I take?)
3 DAYS PRIOR
Have a nice day.
Welcome to the G Championship, the stage of fearless fighters.
This match is in the 72.6-kg weight class, or middleweight.
In the red corner, aka the undefeated dashing fighter, Yoryak Phadetsuek.
[Yoryak, undefeated & dashing, Yoryak Phadetsuek]
How’d it go?
Did your date go well last night?
It’s done.
(Damn. Why? Same as before?)
Yeah. I don’t think asexual exist in this country.
When I refused to sleep with him,
he wanted to break up with me.
Take it easy, Kao.
The one you are looking for might be someone closer to you.
Dee, are you declaring your love for me?
I don’t mind.
But those eyebrows have got to go.
Your bushy eyebrows are such a turn-off.
Jackass.
Are you bullying my eyebrows?
(I know your heart has no room left for anyone else except for…)
(your Dr. Ter.)
Wait. I’ve got to go now.
Your driving was reckless.
How could you not see the car behind before turning right?
You need to be more cautious too.
Do you have the means to take responsibility?
Call the insurance.
No, you're the one who needs to take responsibility for my car.
Call the insurance. You’re wasting my time.
Please stop.
Who the hell are you?
Stay out of this.
No!
Yak!
Throw your punch, for heaven’s sake!
Ouch.
Did you call an ambulance?
Yes.
But they said there were many accidents this morning.
So it’s not here yet.
Yak.
Punch back, come on.
What’re you waiting for?
What are you doing?
There’s likely a fracture in the fibula bone. Press it, please.
Are you a doctor or something?
I'm from the Orthopedic Department.
Specializing in bones and joints.
[Dr. Wandee, Orthopedics, Specializing in bones and joints]
Dr. Wandee.
I'm using an ice press to alleviate your pain and swelling.
If you don't want her to risk permanent damage,
don’t ever try to move her. Got it?
Thank you very much.
Keep pressing it.
That was ruthless.
This knockout took 4.26 seconds less than the previous one, Yak.
But the opponent’s punches are pretty strong, Cher.
Yes, you were at a disadvantage in the beginning.
I was so worried about you, my son.
Hey.
When will you stop calling me your son?
Didn’t you say you love Oyei as if he were your father?
I never said that.
You said that when you were drunk.
I had a video clip of that.
Do you want to see it, my big baby?
Stop it or else I’ll kick you.
Do you dare to kick me?
Yes.
Yei.
Your little bro wants to kick me.
You want to kick my beau?
Yeah, any problem with that, Mr. Oyei Phadetsuek?
I do, Mr. Yoryak Phadetsuek.
I will…
join in the kicking too.
I knew it.
These two brothers are teaming up against me again.
You may kick me,
but you’re sleeping outside tonight.
No, babe.
I never want to kick you.
Yak drives a wedge between us.
How could I dare to kick you?
I still need you to…
Stop your dirty thoughts right now.
I called to book a checkup appointment for you.
Here’s the appointment.
3 p.m. today?
Yes.
But I already have other plans.
Then, take a rain check.
I’m serious about this.
I noticed you couldn’t move your shoulder freely.
You should have a checkup.
Yeah. The sooner you check, the better.
We don’t have to pay a dime. This hospital is our sponsor.
You can see your girl at other times.
Girl?
I meant his fans.
Yak!
Do I need to remind you of your goal?
To be a world champion like you and Dad.
Alright, duly noted.
I'm heading to the hospital.
Alright.
Get back to our camp.
Dee.
I swung by the coffeeshop. I got one for you.
Latte, oatmilk, less sweet, extra shot.
Your usual, right?
Yes.
You remembered?
Of course.
It’s your favorite. How could I not remember?
Thank you.
You look good now.
Always a messy eater.
Sorry.
Being messy doesn't reflect well on our department’s image, huh?
Why apologize?
I actually find it kinda cute.
Oh, I have to get back to my patients.
I’ve just finished up my rounds too.
Later then.
Scream. Scream your lungs out.
Kao, why did you choose to sleep there of all places?
I asked why you slept under there?
I needed somewhere to mend my broken heart.
Did you see? It’s not just me, right?
Dr. Ter is really nice to me.
Listen, Dee. I think you should take it easy.
It's been almost eight years now,
and he's always treated me so nicely.
From day one, my heart's been fluttering like a 3-3.9 Richter quake.
Minor shaking—similar to how people indoors feel the passing of a train.
The day Dr. Ter asked me to work at the same hospital with him,
my heart shook even harder,
reaching a level of 5-5.9 on the Richter scale.
That's a strong shaking in a wider area—things indoors can move.
And when he asked me to buy a room in the same condo as his,
it's like, same freaking condo, you know?
And that's the same condo I live in too!
He helped me pick out every piece of furniture.
He's taken care of everything for me.
He nearly feeds me when we have dinner, you know.
Your heart shakes like a 6-6.9 Richter quake.
It's an intense shaking that can cause damage and collapse.
And did you see what he just did?
My heart is pounding so hard beyond a 7 on the Richter scale.
That's a severe and extreme shaking.
Buildings can be greatly damaged,
things on the ground can be tossed into the air,
just like the heart of Dr. Wandee, my dearest friend.
You really understand me, my friend.
I'm sure Dr. Ter feels the same way.
In that case,
why hasn't he asked you to be his boyfriend yet?
He's a senior,
and he's also the face of this hospital.
It's probably difficult for him to make the first move.
But that's okay.
I'll make it easy for him.
By...
I'll ask him myself.
Just like that?
The next two days mark the anniversary of when we first met.
I'll ask him on that day.
And you know, eight is considered a lucky number–
infinity.
So, this love is infinite, right?
Get ready to celebrate the love between Dr. Ter and me.
I'll look forward to that.
Dr. Dee.
Yes?
Dr. Nop would like to talk to you.
Same thing again?
Yes.
Same time as before?
Exactly the same time.
Yes, Dr. Nop?
Dee, I need your help.
You haven't clocked out yet, have you?
Are you ready, sir?
Sir?
You're not the same doctor.
You seem alright.
I'm not.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be here.
I mean, you're not unconscious or passed out.
Why didn't you answer when I called you?
I was texting, so I didn't answer.
Wouldn't it be polite to at least respond?
Anyway, if you're ready, let's get started.
Can I have a minute? I need to discuss something important with my friend.
Hey, mister.
The time of other patients outside is just as important as yours.
Okay, but I said I need a minute, Doc.
Didn't you hear me?
Hey! That's my phone.
Consider it a social media detox.
It'll help you refocus and be with yourself.
Focus on what’s in front of you.
It also helps boost your mood.
Can you try lifting your arms?
Is this the furthest you can go with this one?
Yes, just this.
Does this hurt?
Um... no.
Ouch.
Didn't you say it didn't hurt?
What happened?
Didn't my record mention I'm a boxer?
So, you got knocked out and fell.
Did you fall on your chest too?
Any difficulty breathing afterward?
I won that bout. Never got knocked out by anyone.
Let me listen to your lungs and heart.
Take a deep breath in.
Can I ask?
You don't watch sports news?
You really don’t know who I am?
You have shoulder tendinitis, but otherwise, you're fine.
Except for the symptom of craving recognition.
If you want treatment for that,
our psychiatry department is efficient.
I can refer you.
Tough doc, huh?
If you were my opponent, you'd be on the floor.
Want me to play along?
Happy to help.
"Oh, I'm really scared."
That patient really got on my nerves. What a jerk.
You weren't actually irritated that Dr. Nop asked you to cover for him and took it out on the patient, right?
No way.
Maybe just a bit.
You should have seen his face.
He's such a narcissist.
I wish I could refer him to your psychiatry department.
Is that so?
Take it easy, man.
Finish up here, head home, and shake off that bad mood.
I've still got my patients to take care of.
See you.
You talked about your patient behind his back.
Wouldn't that be considered impolite?
You're still here.
If I weren't here, I'd miss witnessing this in action.
A doctor in a top hospital in Bangkok
gossipped about his patient’s record.
Should I sue?
Do you have a voice recording?
I wouldn't miss the chance.
Oh,
look at your pale face.
Where's that big-mouthed guy from earlier?
Hello, may I speak with Dr. Wandee?
Hey, I'm not your friend for you to mess around with.
I'm not your friend either.
Go ahead.
Do whatever you want.
I can't be that mean to you.
I hope we don't have to see each other again,
Dr. Wandee.
[Are you still in the hospital? Come see me in the office.]
The hospital has planned to elevate our department to become the premier orthopedic facility.
That’s why our hospital chose to sponsor that outspoken boxer.
Mind your words, Wandee.
You are a doctor, and he’s a patient.
I saw that.
What can we do to help, sir?
Prepare to study abroad.
The hospital will fund a scholarship,
but there’s only one spot available for this first scholarship.
Both of you have been selected as finalists by the board.
Me, really?
I’ll be competing with Dr. Ter for the crown?
Don’t say anything that might jeopardize your chance to win.
You’re a fan of beauty pageants too, I see.
Am I your joking buddy?
I’m kidding.
Take your time to think about it,
and let me know if you're interested in this scholarship.
Got it.
Understood, sir.
I don't care, Yei.
Next time, book me with a different doctor.
This one drives me crazy.
if I see him again, I’m gonna smack him.
(Relax. Let's talk about it when you're back.)
Alright.
Taem, are you finished?
Just a moment.
Your boyfriend is so hot.
He's just a friend, not a boyfriend.
What part are you working on?
Have you solved the problem yet?
Let me see.
I’m yet to get on it.
Here, I finished it for you.
You can hand this over to your professor.
Another assignment must be submitted via email.
I’ll make sure to send it no later than tonight.
Okay.
I’m going to graduate for real this year thanks to your help.
At your service, sir.
You can have more time for boxing.
Leave this to me.
Okay.
Cash or wire?
Alright, I’ll wire it now.
Here.
Thank you for your business.
Looking forward to serving you again.
You are such a money-maker.
You are a tutor for high school students,
and also handle assignments for me.
Being poor is scary.
Taem.
Hmm?
You said…
you would come cheer for me at the ringside.
How come you...
I said I would go if I was free.
But you saw that I had a tutoring job, right?
Yes, I did see, but...
Come on, Yak.
I think it's okay to keep our relationship like this.
Come on, Taem.
I'm yet to finish my delivery to your doorstep.
You returned it before it reached there.
Can't you let me finish it?
I know you too well.
I can’t believe you.
Here, let me explain about your papers.
For this subject—
- Dr. Ter.
- Dee.
We spoke at the same time.
I know.
We share the same mind.
You go first.
The day after tomorrow, you are free in the evening, right?
Yes.
How about grabbing dinner together?
I want to chat with you about something.
Really?
I have something to discuss with you too.
I’ll send you the location of the restaurant later.
Do you want to go there together
or meet there?
Let’s meet there.
I have a meeting with a YouTuber.
Alright,
see you then.
See you.
Kao, my bud.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Nothing's wrong with me.
But these are my last two days of being single.
Are you really going to do it?
Just two days left.
Dr. Ter and I are finally closing the chapter on eight years in the brother zone
and starting a new chapter as the couple of the year.
Can’t wait to see it.
You’ll see it.
Wow.
Is the food here alright?
It's actually pretty good.
I always trust your taste when it comes to food.
Everything I've had with you has been delicious.
Dr. Ter,
I think…
No, I mean we can still be in the relationship.
I still want some physical affection.
But...
I don't want to have sex. Do you get it?
No, I don't.
It's not that difficult to understand.
Kao, come with me.
What, Dee?
Are you okay?
Stop asking me if I’m okay or not.
I’m not okay, so I’m here to see you.
What happened?
Eating with you like this reminds me of the old days.
How long have we known each other?
Holy shit, Dr. Ter started first?
What did you say to him?
Eight years.
Today marks exactly eight years.
You showed him you have an excellent memory too.
Really?
Yes.
On this day eight years ago,
I was a freshman.
And you were the student activities president.
You were the freshman who often passed out at gatherings.
You made me worried then.
I'm still worried about you even now, you know.
Hey,
it sounded like in the right moment, didn’t it?
I know, right?
So I gathered all the courage I have
and…
Dr. Ter.
We’ve known each other for eight years.
I think…
I like you.
And I’m sure you know in what way I like you.
Dee.
I like you too.
But...
I don’t like you in that way.
Damn.
Totally a mood killer.
And what was between us all this time?
We're like brothers.
Brothers?
What about how well you've treated me all this time?
You've consistently taken good care of me.
That's more than what brothers typically do for each other, I think.
Listen, Dee.
I like girls.
I'll let you say it again.
My answer will always be the same.
I like girls.
Dr. Kwan?
Dr. Kwan what?
You like feisty girls
like Dr. Kwan,
like those people talked about you.
That has nothing to do with this.
It has. Then why don’t you like me?
Dee.
Tell me. Regardless of what gender I am,
why don’t you like me?
You are too vanilla for me.
Too vanilla?
Okay.
I get it now.
Me trying to be a decent person to you is too vanilla.
Being decent is vanilla, you say?
Dee. It’s not what I meant.
You are still…
like a brother to me.
So the chapter of being brothers for eight has come to an end.
Not yet.
But nearly.
There’s more.
Dee.
Dee, wait.
Damn, don’t tell me he realized his feelings
and wants you back?
The scholarship…
can you let me have it, bro?
Damn.
Kao,
tonight
I want to get wasted!
So he wanted that scholarship so bad that he accepted my date.
I won’t back down. I will go for it.
Damn. Good boy gone bad.
Aren’t you going to be a good little bro to him anymore?
I’ll be wild tonight.
Hey, Dee.
It’s not the same thing.
You can’t mix up everything like fusion food.
I don’t care.
I’ll be wild tonight.
I’m no longer that plain vanilla kind of guy. Get it?
Alright.
Knock yourself out then.
Am I wild yet?
Do whatever you’re pleased, man.
There must be something I did wrong. I never get it even once.
Why don’t you put the melody to those lyrics too?
Isn’t it strange?
People seemed to be interested in me.
But none approached me.
How come no one invited me home with them?
I’m sure that I’m spicy and tasty.
Listen.
You danced your hip off like that.
I wondered if any guy would want to take you home, you thickhead.
Anyway, I’m just dropping you off at the condo.
I have to go to my sister’s home in Chonburi.
My family has a merit-making ceremony for my father tomorrow.
Okay. Just pull over.
I want to get something in the minimart.
I’ll find my way home later.
Hey, but you’re wasted.
I may find someone who I can get it on with tonight.
Come on, Dee. I beg you.
Pull yourself together and choose wisely.
I know what I am doing.
Pull over. Pull over.
Okay. Easy.
Pull over.
Okay.
Dee,
are you sure you’re okay?
Don’t worry about me. I’ll be fine.
Okay.
You meany man.
What a flirt! Why do you keep haunting me?
You played games with my heart, it hurts like hell.
There’s plenty of fish in the sea.
Surely, there's someone out there who wants me.
- Boxer guy!
- Doc!
Why are you following me?
I’m not following you.
This is my way home.
Where did you go?
A night out.
Are you heading home alone?
Why do you ask?
Hey!
[Free Tasting]
Are you joking with me, Doc?
Pay for this.
I’ll wait outside.
Sir.
Just the condom?
Would you like some gel too?
It's quite essential.
For lubrication, sir.
Damn you.
No one wants me.
Hey, Doc.
What’s going on?
Leave me alone.
I’ll take you home.
Come on.
Go away.
You can’t sleep here.
Come on. Get up.
Go home.
Get off me.
I’ll take you home.
Doc.
Hey,
you can’t sleep here, Doc.
Doc!
Doc.
Sorry, Doc.
TWR.
[Pla-kao]
Sorry again, Doc.
Hello.
(Condo’s security officer?)
No, I’m…
(This is Dr. Plakao speaking.)
(You are with Dr. Wandee, right?)
(If he’s too wasted, can you help take him to his room?)
- Hey, I’m not…
- (Thank you.)
Hello.
Hello?
609.
Here.
You’re home. Get in.
Want to watch some series together?
Ouch.
Want to continue?
Um.
Wait.
Why?
Not feeling up to it anymore?
Well…
I give you 5 seconds.
(Every decision has its binary choices.)
(Which choice should I take?)
It’s all fine.
Some people are born big,
but certain parts might not match the size of the body.
I understand.
Woah.
Now you know why I was named Yoryak aka giant.
Want to continue?
Yes.
Oi, oi!
What’s wrong, Doc?
Cramp.
Cramp?
I’ve got a leg cramp.
Ouch.
Here?
This spot?
Yes.
Massage it.
Oi.
You get cramps often?
Um,
probably because I haven’t been getting enough sleep lately.
I see.
I used to get them too.
Anyway,
you weren’t scared of my thing, so you got a cramp, right?
What?
People always seem surprised and scared of my baby.
Really?
It’s not that scary.
Are you scared?
Not really.
How’s your shoulder?
It's getting better.
Your medicine must be effective, I guess.
Can I check?
- Should we try again?
[Ordinary Days That Will Never Be the Same Again]
Thanks for taking me home.
Don’t feel bad about it.
One-night stand?
Once is enough.
Over.
Have you already made a decision about the scholarship?
I’m in.
At this rate, I would be a coward to back down.
I miss you so much, Grandma.
Tell me honestly, are you still single?
Find someone.
How about we become friends with benefits?