I’ll be your compatible opponent.
I won’t pull a punch, Senior Ter.
So which security guard carried you to your room last night?
I didn’t really remember.
How about we become friends with benefits?
What are the rules between us?
We won’t intrude on each other’s private matters.
We meet up and have sex.
But you don’t allow me to kiss you, right?
Do you allow this?
Tired?
Still okay.
Hang in there.
More?
What is this pendant’s shape?
Two Ys
Yor-Yak?
Yes.
A strange name, but cool.
Yoryak.
You have a nice word for me.
The world is probably collapsing.
Don’t exaggerate.
Why don’t you take a shower? In a rush?
Um.
I’d rather shower at my boxing gym.
I should get there fast or else Yei will scold me.
Yei?
Who is Yei?
It’s okay if you don’t want to tell me.
No worries. I’ll tell you.
He’s my big brother. His name is Oyei.
He always acts more like a father than a brother.
And when he coaches me, he’s as ferocious as a fierce dog.
If your brother is like your father,
you must be like your mother.
Maybe. I’m not sure.
I’m heading out now.
Yak.
Don’t forget this cap, you are the legendary AC guy.
Thanks for letting me serve you.
Please call me if you need my service again.
Of course, I will.
See you.
(Phadetseuk)
Yak.
Hm?
Where’s your necklace?
Necklace?
Do you wear necklaces now?
I never saw you wear one before.
I'm giving it a try.
A guy gave it to you?
Yes.
I don’t know.
I probably left it somewhere.
You don’t know, or you don’t want us to know?
The one you slept with while I was in Chonburi?
How did you know?
I don’t know who he is,
but I could smell you got lucky.
Smart ass.
Are you a doctor or a dog exactly?
Yak is a sugar daddy.
He's so generous when dating. You also know that.
At which stage are you with the person you gave the necklace to?
I said I didn’t know where I left it.
Really?
Alright.
I gave it to someone.
But we’re not an item.
Just a fuck buddy.
Fuck buddy?
What’s so funny?
I like that, ‘fuck buddy’.
It sounds romantic.
At least you consider that person your buddy.
Right?
Buddy.
Buddy!
Buddy. I see.
Are you in a relationship with that guy?
Or is it just casual sex?
Casual, of course.
I'm not ready for any kind of relationship with anyone now.
It's exhausting.
Really?
But it seems like more than just a one-night stand.
He even gave you this necklace.
Just for pleasure, I think.
So you hang out a lot
with the same person
not changing partners, right?
Hey, Kao. I’m not your patient.
Want to be one? Be my guest.
No, I'm not changing partners.
I don’t sleep around.
So it developed from a one-night stand to friends with benefits.
I’m not saying it's a bad thing. It's totally normal.
I have many patients doing this.
But...
be careful.
Don't
watch too many romantic movies
or else you might start expecting
that it could develop into a serious relationship.
Although there's a 27% chance of that happening.
Okay.
Though Wandee means a good day,
I don’t always think things are good and rosy.
I can distinguish between love, relationship,
or just pleasure.
Clear?
I think you have a good chance of getting this scholarship.
Dr. Wandee.
Dr. Plakao.
Hi.
Aren't we headed to the men's room? Let's go.
Come on.
This is such a great acting talent
from this year’s Oscar winner, Dr. Wandee.
He smiles like he’s strong,
but his heart is completely shattered.
Are you having so much fun?
Dr. Wandee is really cute.
His skin is smooth and clear like glass.
If he had chosen dermatology, he would have done so well in that field.
I agree.
But I heard he would go to further his studies in orthopedics like you.
I don’t know about that.
Where did you hear it from?
Just some staff chitchatting.
I see.
Dr. Ter, thank you for the souvenir.
Do you like it?
I do.
I like both the gift and the giver.
They look good together, unlike…
Unlike what, Ood?
Unlike what Nurse Noinong told us.
I’m sorry.
I haven’t been here for the past few days.
I’ve been in intense training.
I understand. Don’t feel bad about it.
We can meet when we’re both free.
I’ve been quite busy lately too,
dealing with patient cases and hitting the books.
Not to mention all those campaign meetings.
What brings you here today though?
Got free time?
At first, I didn’t.
But after...
hearing this voice, I couldn’t resist not coming here.
(You must’ve been busy. When you’re free, come meet me too.)
Look, someone is missing me.
No, I’m not.
I just play along with your game.
Someone sent me this seductive clip when I lost touch with him.
Not seductive.
I just wanted to show I was busy training hard.
Really?
If you miss me, just say “I miss you.”
That’s simple.
Say it.
Hey.
The light bulb.
You haven’t changed it.
Yoryak, don’t change the subject.
Hey, it’s not good to leave it like that.
Let me help change it for you.
“I miss you.” Say it.
I miss you.
Happy now?
I won.
You like to win that much, huh?
Yes.
That’s my bad habit.
Winning over someone makes me feel sexy.
Really, Doctor?
Here.
Time to change the light bulb.
Gosh. You like to dictate too.
Here.
Let’s see if it will light up.
Woah.
You are so talented.
Highly skilled.
Surely.
That’s surely fake.
You actually can change that yourself, right?
I’m not sure.
What’re you up to, Cher?
You seem quite serious.
I’m working on the financial stuff.
There are so many numbers that I’m frowning without realizing.
Can I assist you with anything?
Is Oyei around?
I think he’s out running an errand.
What’s up?
Well, my father is sick.
I want to ask Oyei if I can get an advance payment.
I don’t think there should be any problem with that.
This is not something Oyei doesn’t allow.
I’ll let him know when he’s back.
Thanks a lot, Cher.
Harder.
Harder, Yei.
Harder?
Harder.
Harder!
Is that hard enough?
You pervy man.
Hey, people might see us.
My beau is cute.
Why?
It’s embarrassing.
It’s not. I own this place. What to be afraid of?
What to be afraid of?
Here.
Thank you.
Hey.
Jo came to talk to you about advance payment, right?
Yes. I must give it to him.
His father is sick.
Will there be enough left to pay off the debts?
During the Covid shutdown,
our boxers couldn’t participate in any matches.
You had to take out a loan to cover the expenses.
Come on.
That matter was sorted out a long time ago.
Don’t worry about it.
I’ve already managed everything. There should be no problem.
Alright, Mr. Have-Everything-Managed.
How about this?
If we don’t have enough money this month,
why don’t we borrow from my mother?
No, I don’t want to.
I already got the gold shop lady’s son to be mine
and even have him work for my gym.
I feel bad enough.
I don’t want to impose on her any more than I already do.
Then If anyone shows interest in our boxing courses,
I’ll sell them all.
All the boxers in our gym must become trainers and must not refuse.
You must help me as well.
Understood?
Okay.
If anyone dares to object Madam Cher,
they’ll have to deal with Mr. Oyei.
Stop it.
I’m serious about what I said.
You have given me your word.
You must not break it.
Understood?
Don’t do this, Cher.
Why?
Did I hurt you?
No.
You look so damn cute.
Yei.
Peekaboo!
Where is Namphu the strong boy?
That’s me, I’m Namphu the strong boy.
Let me see if you’re really strong or not.
Can I check?
Yes.
You are indeed a strong boy.
I told you I’m strong.
You deserve a reward for being this strong.
What will I get?
Here they are.
Tada!
Which one do you like?
I like this one.
Thank you so much, Dr. Wandee.
You’re welcome.
When my son told me he was in pain,
I didn't know what to do.
I tried not to cry in front of him.
You are a very strong mother.
No wonder Namphu is so optimistic.
The cancer has spread to his spine.
Is there any chance for him to recover
and have a normal life like other kids?
We will do our best, ma’am.
Even the best can’t make my son the same again.
Ma’am.
It’s always harder to repair than to rebuild.
But I will do everything I can
to help him stand again with his own strength,
and minimize his dependence on others.
If he can do that,
he will have a sense of pride in himself
and not lose his self-worth.
Dr. Apichart,
our future premier orthopedic center
will have a more advanced osteosarcoma department
equipped with more cutting-edge equipment, right?
Yes.
But all those advanced medical devices may be ineffective
if we don’t have skilled enough physicians.
What’s up?
Hi there.
I’m at my uni, not training at the gym.
So, no exclusive video clip for you today.
I told you, didn’t I?
Just say “I miss you” when you miss me.
Who’s missing you? Don’t be funny.
Hold on, Doc.
What’s going on? Your eyes look swollen.
Did you cry?
What happened?
Nothing.
I’m fine.
I’m just letting my thoughts wander.
Loaded tasks?
A bit.
Are you feeling very tired?
It feels so nice to have someone ask if you’re tired when you are.
Doc, seriously, are you okay?
I’m okay.
Nothing to be worried about.
Anyway, are you coming to my place tonight?
I’m waiting for you to ask.
Well then, please wait for your dinner from this delivery rider.
I’ll be waiting.
Okay.
Dr. Wandee.
Yes?
Some people want to start a war.
Rumor has it that he confessed and got rejected outright.
What’s wrong with Dr. Wandee?
He got rejected. He transitioned into a rival.
Look at him now.
He’s acting disrespectfully to his own senior.
You all seem to enjoy trash-talking.
How about some defamation lawsuits?
Dr. Wandee.
Hey, why stop now?
Ah, I get it. You’re saving your voice for defending in court.
What? Are you going to sue me?
On what grounds?
Everything I said is true.
Do you have evidence?
If you don’t, that’s a groundless rumor.
That’s the evidence.
What are you talking about?
Hi, Dr. Ter.
We’re talking about what people are saying about Dr. Wandee.
They say he applied for this scholarship
because he confessed to you and was rejected at a restaurant.
What is this about?
Where did you hear that rumor from?
It’s not a rumor since it’s not groundless.
But this can be seen from miles away how Dr. Wandee thinks about you.
What do I think about him?
I don’t think about him at all.
Are you sure?
I’m sure.
And also…
Read my lips.
I’m already seeing someone.
That can’t be real.
It’s real.
Right, guys?
Yes.
Dr. Wandee is already seeing someone.
It’s the owner of the necklace on his neck.
Now stop talking about me.
You should spend this time doing your work and taking care of patients.
Dee.
Dee!
Where are you going?
Dee.
Dee!
Dee, wait.
Dee.
I have no involvement in that.
Thanks for telling me.
I knew you wouldn’t do something like that.
But Nurse Noinong, your head supporter,
I think this is going too far.
I’m starting my campaign soon.
Going forward, let’s play by the rules.
They're using rumors to discredit you.
Are we still stuck in the politics of the '80s?
What an old trick.
I know, right?
Anyway, this could seriously affect the votes for the scholarship.
I’m not shaken by it.
It’s still a long way before the vote day.
What will you do now?
You made them believe you're seeing someone.
Where will you find a guy to be your date now?
Do you already have someone in mind?
No.
But I can find someone to play that role.
Cheers.
Yak.
How about we pretend to be in a relationship for four months?
Like announcing it to the public?
Can we?
Please, do me this little favor.
It’s necessary for me.
I think...
we should revisit what's between us.
We agreed to be friends with benefits
because we didn't want a relationship, right?
Um.
But here you're asking me to be in a fake relationship with you?
Correct. 10 points to you.
Take back your damn test paper.
I don’t want to do it anymore.
Hey, why?
Come on, Yak. Please help me.
It’s not much to ask.
Just four months. It’s not that long.
But this is too much to ask from me.
I'm a hopeful world championship boxer.
How can I announce to the public that I’m dating…
dating a guy? I don’t think that’s good for me.
But this is a new era.
No one really cares about this kind of thing.
But I care.
I think I should drop out of this.
Hey,
Yak.
Yak!
Come on, Yak.
It’s just to let people in my hospital know.
Other people won’t find out. I can assure you that.
But you just said it yourself.
We are in this era.
It’s not possible, seriously.
Once it’s out there, you cannot control it.
Once it’s released to the public, you can never truly contain it.
But I said I can assure you, didn’t I?
Doc.
We see each other because we want to have fun, don’t we?
But this isn't fun anymore for me.
Let’s put an end to it here.
Yak.
Yak!
Yoryak!
Why did you stop, Jo?
I’m exhausted.
I think I’ve skipped more than a thousand times already.
Let me take a break.
Alright. Rest if you want.
But you must try to shed some weight.
You were almost over the weight limit when you last weighed in.
You know?
Got it.
Hi.
Are you looking for someone?
I’m here to see Yoryak.
Is he here?
Hey, Doc.
Don’t you think you're crossing a line here?
You came to find me at my gym?
I told you I didn’t want to do that.
I understand that you don’t want to do it.
But if you don’t help me,
I’m going to lose this scholarship.
This scholarship is really important to me.
If I don’t get it,
I don’t know if I'll ever have enough money to study abroad in this lifetime.
Cut the drama.
Doctors are rich.
Don’t use money as your reason.
How about this?
I pay you.
How much do you want? Just say the number.
I’ll transfer to your account right away.
What for?
I’m not in need of money.
Go hire someone else.
Why are you going after me?
Please.
Just leave.
Yak!
(Open Now, Private Training 10 sessions/month only ฿4,500!)
(6 courses, 6 months, no fixing time ฿25,000)
What? Six courses!
Yes, on one little condition.
You’ll get it.
Are you going to teach him or not?
No.
If he really wants to have a boxing class here,
let other guys teach him.
Then I think I’ll have to cancel my courses.
Please wait a bit.
People must not give up or give in on hopes too easily!
Come on, Yak!
Stop it. I’m not gonna teach him and that’s that.
Hello, Cher.
Yak is adamant with his decision.
You must not let him.
You already gave me your word.
(You would do everything to help me sell my courses.)
But Yak completely refused. How could I make him?
That’s your problem.
I’m going back to my home.
Don’t come get me.
Hey, Cher.
Please wait a bit more, Doctor.
I guarantee that you will have Yoryak as your personal trainer.
I promise that when you are here tomorrow,
you’ll get to see Yoryak definitely.
Definitely?
Yes, trust me.
I’ll wait for your sake then.
Would it be possible to pay for the course fee now?
Sure.
Payment done!
Yak.
Let’s settle this in the Phadetseuk family way.
If you defeat me,
you don’t have to teach Dr. Wandee.
But if you lose to me,
you must teach him.
Deal?
Deal.
Six courses are at stake!
Or else I’ll go back to my home.
Move toward him.
Go. Move.
You’ve got this, Yei.
Come on, Yei!
For the six courses!
Here.
Thank you, Trainer.
Please give me advice.
Wow.
Do you want me to wear this for the class?
Yes.
Cher would like you to post a picture of yourself wearing it
and tag Phadetseuk Boxing Club in your post.
Will do.
Don’t smile at me.
Let me make it clear here.
Me accepting to be your trainer
has nothing to do with that request of yours.
I haven’t said a thing about it.
Be serious when learning.
You’re quite strict,
Mr. Trainer Yoryak.
You’ll see a stricter me soon.
Baby, let me give it to you
Baby, I assure you it won’t be dull
It won’t hurt you at all, ahh
Baby, let me guarantee
Baby, once you try it, you’ll get down on your knees
Begging to be with me
I never thought boxing training could be this tiring.
You don’t have the basics.
As you learn, your body’s fitness can improve.
That’s it for today.
Hey. Don’t go yet.
What more do you want?
It’s been days that you haven’t come to watch a series at my place.
Stop it.
Stop seducing me.
It’s over between us.
Then tell me.
What do I need to do to get you to help me?
I’ll agree to be your fake boyfriend,
only if within the next five minutes,
you can land a punch on me.
Just one punch?
You’re giving me too much edge.
Yak!
What’re you doing? I’m right here.
I’m serious this time.
Now you can stop asking me to be your fake boyfriend.
Doc.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
I’m just exhausted.
What do you want now?
Hold on.
Where are you taking me to?
(9 Wonton Noodles)
Thank you.
Get a new one if you want to have it too.
Don’t stare at me.
I can’t fully enjoy my food.
No, I don’t want to eat it.
Don’t tell me you never had this?
Are you crazy? How could I never have this simple dish?
I’m just wondering why you keep me company.
This is really delicious.
It’s so so good.
Alright. I can have a bite.
I was trying to be strict with my IF program.
Have this.
You exercised a lot earlier.
Eat this. You need to reach the necessary protein level.
Wow. It’s yummy.
You said you had it before.
That was long ago.
What an excuse artist.
Go ahead. Eat it with me.
This is nice.
Doc.
Why did you accept my challenge?
Weren’t you scared of getting hit in the face?
I wasn’t scared.
I knew you would never hurt me.
That's confidence.
Yes.
Doc.
Hm?
Can I ask?
About this fake relationship,
why does it have to be me?
That's probably because you never ignored me.
What do you mean?
That night.
When I was so drunk sitting by the trash.
You could have easily left me there alone.
But you didn’t.
Instead, you carried me on your back to my condo.
And then there was that other night
when some bad guys got me drunk.
Someone was there to save me.
Without that person’s embrace that night,
I couldn’t imagine what would have happened to me.
Also that person was so kind that he woke up early and made me breakfast.
Though the look of it hardly qualified as breakfast.
How did you know it was me?
Have you heard of a gadget called CCTV on this planet?
What?
Do you have CCTV installed in your room?
Are you nuts?
It’s the Condo’s CCTV.
That’s a relief.
So,
if I were to look for someone to be my fake boyfriend,
to shut up those mean colleagues who like to trash-talk me–
insulting me, saying I compete for the scholarship
to disrespect a senior after being rejected–
I couldn’t think of anyone else but you.
Doc.
I…
I understand.
Actually, this matter doesn’t really concern you.
I shouldn’t drag you into it.
Can you forget about it?
I’ll find a way to deal with it somehow.
Doc.
What are you doing?
You successfully landed a punch on me.
Let’s be fake boyfriends.
Wow, fireworks.
It’s not festival time, how come there are fireworks?
I don’t know either. Probably a new mall has just opened.
Never mind.
Isn’t it beautiful?
Um.
Four months, right?
Yes, four months.
It’s around the same time as my world championship fight.
If I can make it to the finals.
I’m sure you will reach the finals.
We both have our own goals to achieve.
Mr. Soon-To-Be World Champion Boxer.
Go get it too.
Soon-To-Be Scholarship Winner Doctor.
I can’t believe him.
He confessed to his crush but got rejected
so he decided to challenge that crush without any respect for seniority.
Where did you hear that from?
When he confessed,
Noinong saw him.
He told me every little detail.
What’s funny is that
when he got exposed, he made up a story about dating someone.
I couldn’t believe he would go this far.
That’s not what happened, Nurse Oud.
Come on, Dr. Ter. Stop protecting him.
He’s a disrespectful person.
Nurse Oud.
How could we vote for this kind of person to get the scholarship?
Right?
Right.
It must be you, Dr. Ter.
You have all the qualities. You’re kind.
You deserve the scholarship.
Am I right?
Yes.
You can compliment someone without tearing down others, you know?
What I said is 1000% true, isn’t it?
Well, we’ll find out what is true soon, I guess.
Yoryak Phadetseuk!
Doc.
Yak.
Take this.
Do you like it?
You’re good at this.
Let’s make our pretense seem as real as possible,
darling.
Did you see Dr. Ter’s face?
It was so damn satisfying.
He was giving a buttface.
And those nurses too.
They were all flabbergasted.
It’s time to celebrate our first step of being fake boyfriends.
I’ll show you my cooking skills.
You can cook?
I’m a student of Chef Yu.
Chef Yu?
Yu eat it if you can. If you can't,  that's a Yu problem!
Is this how you like to play?
Yak.
Do you really know how to do that?
Yes.
Let me do it for you.
No.
I want to do it.
Let me do it.
No. You’re not good at doing it.
Let me try first.
Look.
You need to do it like this.
Put the chili paste in the pan, only half of that.
Stir it to release the fragrance, then pork.
It’s burning.
No, it’s not.
Stay out of it.
Put the mortar away.
Then go clear those.
It looks good.
But…
are you sure it’s edible?
Of course.
Look.
Wow.
So delicious.
Really?
It’s that good?
It doesn’t look like it.
In what universe is this considered delicious?
Isn’t it good?
It’s overly salty, Doc.
This could be lethal for people with kidney problems, you know.
I think I went a little overboard with the salt.
Give me water.
Sorry.
Go learn cooking again.
Forget Chef U and find a new teacher.
But you said it was good.
You are a big fan of salty food, right?
No, I’m good.
No, you’re not.
Another bite, come on.
I’m done.
Just a small bite.
It’s big.
It’s too big.
You already experienced a bigger bite.
(Fake Boyfriends)
You came to see Dr. Wandee so early in the morning.
I actually slept here last night.
About Yoryak, your fake boyfriends.
You don’t really need to do that.
What?
Sleep here?
Tonight, try not to go overboard tonight with your activity.
Dr. Ter has seen my Story.
Isn’t that too fast of him?
Are you jealous of me?
Will you be my boyfriend?
Yes!