You made them believe you're seeing someone.
Where will you find a guy to be your date now?
How about we pretend to be in a relationship for four months?
But this is too much to ask from me.
Just leave.
Yak.
I’ll agree to be your fake boyfriend,
only if within the next five minutes, you can land a punch on me.
Can I ask? About this fake relationship,
why does it have to be me?
You successfully landed a punch on me.
Let’s be fake boyfriends.
I’m here, Mom.
I won today too, Mom.
Mom.
I’m here, Mom.
I’m here.
Can you please stay with me?
I’m here, Mom.
I’m sorry, Mom.
I’m sorry.
You awake?
Um.
Still hours left until dawn.
Go back to sleep.
Darling.
Plakao.
Dee’s not with you?
I always see you two together.
Ah, he has his boyfriend to be with now.
He’s not clingy to me anymore.
He told me he liked me not long ago,
and then a few days later,
he introduced his new boyfriend.
Isn't that a bit too soon?
Don’t you think?
Uh…
Not really.
Totally normal.
You should know that he can move on fast.
But…
It seems way too fast this time.'
Why do you care?
You don’t like him that way, do you?
I’m just asking.
Dr. Ter.
If you genuinely want the best for Dee.
Now that he’s seeing someone and seems happy,
shouldn't you be happy for him?
Hello, Kwan.
You’re quite a big eater.
You also bought takeout for later.
Why not?
It’s delicious.
You can’t help but eat it over and over, right?
You and your dirty mind.
I made this sandwich for you.
I noticed that you don’t have morning shifts.
Thank you so much.
You really don’t have to. I feel bad for inconveniencing you.
Not at all.
I usually make this for myself.
I just made a few extra today.
Thank you.
I hope you enjoy it.
Hi, Dr. Dee.
Where did you come from?
We went to buy some rice porridge.
What brings you here, Dr. Kwan?
She dropped by to give me this sandwich.
Dr. Ter told me he wanted to have it.
You came to see Dr. Wandee so early in the morning.
Ah, I didn’t.
I actually slept here last night.
Yes.
Please excuse us then.
See you at the hospital, Dr. Kwan.
See you.
They have really good chemistry together.
Doc.
Are you okay?
With what?
Dr. Ter.
With that lady doc.
You seemed pretty tense back there.
Who? I wasn’t.
Give me a break. I don’t feel anything.
Okay. I’ll try to believe that you don’t feel anything.
I said I don’t feel anything.
Stop it, Yak.
You don’t feel anything?
Why use that tone though?
You just don’t want to admit it.
(You wanted to have this, so I got it for you.
This place is really good. Try it. - Dee…)
Wow.
This is seriously delicious.
You eat a lot. You might gain weight.
That’s alright.
I’m trying to gain more weight.
Yei wants me to climb up a weight class.
That’s why you go hard on this.
So you really don’t have feelings for Dr. Ter anymore?
Come on, Yak.
Do you have OCD or what?
Wait.
You keep asking me that.
Are you jealous?
What crap are you talking about?
Feeling jealous is what I’m talking about.
I don’t feel jealous, but worried.
Someone might end up getting drunk and crying beside the trash again.
It’ll become my trouble to carry you back.
But from the way I see it, it looks like someone who is jealous.
I’m not jealous.
We’re not real boyfriends.
Why would I get jealous?
Really?
More importantly,
I already have someone I like.
You’re already seeing someone?
Really? I just realized I never asked.
Were you already dating someone when I asked you to be my fake boyfriend?
I’m not,
otherwise, I wouldn’t have agreed to be your fake boyfriend.
But you said you have someone you like.
That’s right.
Her name is Taemrak.
She’s a junior at my university.
She helps me with my studies.
What a cute name–Taemrak.
Her nature is cute too.
I like her.
But…
I don’t think she likes me that way.
What makes you think that she doesn’t like you?
I’m not quite sure. She seems indifferent towards me, I think.
When she’s with someone else, she’s more cheerful and lively.
Have you tried to win her over?
Like making a serious move on her.
Not yet.
I’m afraid of losing her.
You don’t know how to flirt, do you?
Do you want me to teach you?
Come on.
Do you have the audacity to teach anyone?
You can’t even successfully win Dr. Ter’s heart.
Oi.
Stop rubbing that in my face.
You might as well stab me with this knife.
Alright. Show me how you make a move on Taemrak.
Hey, Taem.
So what are we to each other?
We’ve known each other for so long.
Can you make it clear to me?
No wonder you keep failing to win her heart.
That’s so lackluster.
What should I do then?
You must be a little softer.
Tell her how you feel about her first.
You can’t just ask what you are to each other.
No woman would have an answer for that.
Really?
Hey.
Hand grab?
You should ask first if you can hold her hand.
Let’s assume that she allows me.
Okay.
Then?
Taem,
we’ve known each other for quite some time.
Not good. Still the same pattern.
Let me finish it.
Taem,
whenever we’re together,
every moment we share,
from the first day until now,
I call it happiness.
So…
if it’s possible at all,
can I have a chance to take care of you?
Would you be my date?
What’s up, Yei?
(Hey, Yak. Your next fight is settled.)
(Let’s talk about the details when you’re back.)
Okay, got it. I’ll be right there.
You have another bout coming?
Yes.
Anyway, Doc.
Did you like that?
Do you think Taem will like that approach?
Ah.
I think she probably likes it.
Really?
Yes!
That gives me energy for training.
This one is gonna be a bit tough.
You must gain weight to move up to this weight class
because there are no more opponents left for you to fight,
only foreign boxers.
Okay.
Why do you have to move him up a weight class?
Isn’t it too risky?
That’s alright, Cher.
Yei needs money.
Yak…
We’re not a big boxing camp.
Time is short.
Yak has only four months until the world championship tournament.
We need money.
Let’s do it, bro.
I can handle this, Cher.
By the way, Yei.
After this fight,
can I have a brief break?
I want to wrap up my studies.
I want everything sorted before the championship.
Sure, my bro.
But I still don’t understand.
Why do you keep pursuing your studies?
You don’t need a degree to be a boxer.
Just let me finish it.
Let’s continue watching.
Your mother seemed like a very kind person.
Um.
She’s the kindest in the world.
I kinda miss her.
By the way,
Dr. Wandee has confirmed his class this evening.
Alright. I’m not gonna bail.
I know.
You haven’t been objecting to teaching him lately.
He must be really special
or else you wouldn’t have given him your necklace.
I gave it to him for another reason.
Oh, really?
I thought he was the one.
Come on.
You know who I have feelings for.
I used to know.
But now I’m not quite certain who exactly you have feelings for.
Don’t be absurd.
I’m not someone who changes his mind easily.
Coach.
Keep going.
Can I have a break, Coach?
I can’t do it anymore.
Are you okay? Your face is red.
Feeling unwell?
But no fever.
Let me grab my stuff to check on you.
Doc.
No need to.
Why?
If you have a fever, I can give you treatment.
Your next match is coming.
I’m fine.
You’re not fine.
Your face and ears are red.
I’m really fine.
I just…
find you cute.
What’s wrong with you?
What’s with the sudden flattery?
Now, your face is turning red.
What’s wrong?
Are you not feeling well?
Want me to grab a thermometer to check if you have a fever?
I told you not to tease me.
Dare to tease me?
Yak.
Hey, Taem.
You’re here.
Sorry. Did I make you wait too long?
This needs to be submitted on Tuesday before noon.
It’s an assignment from Prof.
And these…
the study notes for the test next week.
You can just read through them,
and I can assure you that you’ll pass the test.
Okay.
Woah.
You even highlighted them for me?
Um.
Thank you so much,
My beloved Taem.
Please change ‘my beloved’ to cash for me.
What a mood-killer.
Are you in the middle of coaching?
Your client is really cute.
Not cute at all.
He’s one stubborn student.
Hey, Taem.
Would you like to stay for dinner?
I’ll have Cher prepare some more food.
Um…
I’d rather not.
The food here is just chicken breast and boiled eggs.
Those are all good stuff.
Kidding.
I’ve got some errands to run for the Student Council.
I see.
You are quite dedicated to the Student Council.
Of course.
The council helps monitor the rights for all students.
I must dedicate myself.
That’s what Student Council President Ohm said to me.
Yes?
I’m done. I’ll go with you.
Wait. Wait for me.
Ohm gave me a ride. He’s waiting outside.
I’m going back to campus with him.
No need to rush, Taem.
I can wait.
I already let the team know we’d be there a bit late.
I’m done here. Wait.
I’m good.
I’ve got to go now.
If you have questions on any points, text me.
Happy to explain them all.
Thanks.
Okay.
See you.
A jealous man has been sighted at Phadetseuk Boxing Club.
A man who will be ordered to do more situps
has been sighted at Phadetseuk Boxing Club.
Come on, Coach. I’m pooped.
No, you must do it. Now.
Taem seems very lovely.
You should make your move fast
before that cute-looking guy steals her from you.
I'm counting to five. Start doing situps.
Taem seems to have feelings for you
otherwise she wouldn’t help you with your assignment.
- Come on. - 	4
No.
Fine, I’ll do it.
Were you a calculator in your previous life?
You seem to be fond of counting so much.
Hold my ankles!
Got it.
Stop whining.
Who do you think is more handsome, me or that fella?
That young man, definitely.
He carries himself well.
He seems to be much more decent too.
Are you taking a dig at me here?
No.
You asked me.
I just stated the fact.
Hey, Doc.
Can you help me dress to look better than that guy?
In return for me agreeing to be your fake boyfriend.
What are you scheming?
I’m taking a shot with Taem as you suggested.
Great move.
You've come this far,
might as well give it a shot now.
I know, right?
Let’s do it and see if it works out in my favor or not.
Enough, Doc.
Don’t put in too much water.
It’s too hot.
Hot temperatures are not good for our bodies, you know.
Yak seems happy when he's with Dr. Dee, don't you think?
Yeah.
So, who does he have feelings for now?
Dr. Dee or Taemrak?
Well, I think
we have to let him figure out his own feelings
before he can make a choice.
Do you mind, though?
I don't mind at all.
When I introduced you to him, he didn’t have any objections.
Whoever my brother loves, I'll love that person too.
You sound handsome.
If I weren't handsome,
I wouldn't have won the heart of someone as cute as you.
Now give me a cheek to kiss.
Why do you want to kiss me? Stop.
Why can’t I?
I haven’t taken a shower, and neither have you.
You’re sticky.
Then give me a shower.
No.
Come on.
Come on. Please.
No.
You do it alone.
I can’t scrub my back.
We’ve been together for 10 years.
Our sex life isn’t exciting anymore.
It’s probably because we've gotten used to it.
Doing the same thing over and over becomes boring.
It makes me lose my sexual desire.
I’ve tried many things actually–
chains or handcuffs,
wigs, backdoor, watching porn,
I did everything, even if it's not really me.
It still doesn’t work.
Maybe I should try having sex with someone else?
To be in a relationship,
I understand that sex can become an important element,
especially for certain people.
But for others, sex may not hold the same importance.
Let’s slowly try to figure out
what can be a bridge to reconnect you both
and revive the passion in your sexual life.
Hey, Dee.
Within the last five minutes,
you've been sighing like ten million times already, you know.
Anything you want to share with me?
I think I find myself
getting jealous over Yak.
I know he and I are in a fake relationship.
Somehow, I get jealous of his crush.
Shit. That’s serious.
Not just that.
I gave my word to Yak
that I would help him pursue that girl he likes.
Gosh, Dee!
You are so you, man!
Why do you complicate the thing that’s already complicated?
Kao…
What should I do?
First of all,
you must hold off on your heart
before it gets hurt even more.
Dee, you tend to mix things up and add drama to them.
I think you should take some time for yourself
and sort out your own feelings.
Figure out what really bothers you.
What's causing it? Or who's causing it?
Mind if I join your swim, Doc?
I thought you would be late, so I came swimming here.
I started my training early and finished up quick.
Don’t you have to see Taemrak today?
No. I didn’t go to uni today.
Doc.
After my next fight,
we should start our plan to win Taem’s heart.
Why “we”?
Come on, Doc.
You agreed to help me.
But this is something you should take on solo.
No, Doc.
I’ve been trying to win her over for years,
but she doesn’t like me back.
With your help, I might stand a better chance.
Come on.
Please help me.
Think of it as
repayment for my assistance with your mission.
Alright.
Great.
You don’t really need to use this method.
What are you talking about?
If it’s about the scholarship, I think I’ve made myself clear.
About Yoryak,
your fake boyfriend.
What do you mean fake?
He’s my real boyfriend.
You also saw him staying over at my place the other night.
He stayed over just so I’d see?
What do you mean?
Doesn’t it seem too coincidental?
How coincidental that the boxer guy showed up with flowers
right when everyone was on break.
How coincidental that he and you appear
at the same time I usually go to the condo’s fitness room.
And what’s the coincidence today
that made you come talk to me about this?
This is not a coincidence. I wanted to be here.
You really don’t need to do that.
I have my case to take care of.
Excuse me.
Can’t you wait for me a little longer?
I was just confused before.
Now, I’m trying to get everything to fall into place.
Stop doing this.
It doesn’t work with me anymore.
I have Yoryak now.
And I’ll move forward to compete for this scholarship with you.
1 2
Okay!
We've gone to this length, and he still doesn't believe us?
I can’t believe it either.
He thought he could pressure me into giving up on the scholarship.
You think?
Apparently.
Don’t forget he’s smart and sneaky.
He managed to make me think he had feelings for me for years.
He got me to do all sorts of stuff for him for eight years.
He's that manipulative?
Dr. Ter, really?
Yep.
It's not what you built up in your head, is it?
Hey, Yak.
Whose side are you on?
Your side, of course.
So, how do we make him believe?
Actually, I've got an idea.
I don’t think the real cunning schemer is Dr. Ter.
It’s you, Doc.
Yoryak.
Alright, I'll stop teasing.
So, what's the plan? Tell me.
What?
Sleep here?
Yes.
Dr. Dee will stay over tonight.
We have to discuss a few things.
like training,
and also my shoulder problem.
Yes.
Dr. Dee has some new physiotherapy techniques to teach me
before the championship fights.
Is that so?
Yes, it is.
Right, Doc?
Right.
Actually, there are a lot of physiotherapy exercises he needs to practice.
Given our clashing schedules,
tonight is the night to do it.
Ah.
What do you think, Cher?
What?
Ah, I have no problem.
Well then, I’ll go prepare a room for you.
It’s okay, Cher.
Tonight, Doc.
Dr. Dee will sleep in my room.
Yes, it’s totally fine.
I’m pretty chill, right?
I can sleep in his bed.
No, Doc.
Don’t show my face.
I know.
Let’s do this. Give me your hand.
We can hold hands instead.
Put them here.
Okay.
You’re posting it on your Story?
Yes, I want Dr. Ter to see it.
Doc.
How about this?
What?
Lay on my lap.
I’ll hold the camera.
When you’re on my lap, I’ll take your picture.
This way it will look more romantic.
Alright.
Like this.
Yes. Good.
Okay now?
Now look into my eyes.
And do this cutie patootie face.
Yes.
Can I have my phone back?
I want to post my Story.
Hey.
Dr. Ter has seen my Story. Yes!
What?
Isn’t that too fast of him?
Does he have notifications on?
Hey.
Are you jealous of me?
Who’s jealous?
You’re talking nonsense.
It’s obvious that you are jealous.
I’m not.
I totally saw that you are jealous.
I said I’m not.
You are.
I’m not.
Yeah.
This boxing club was founded in B.E. 2532,
as you see on the t-shirt.
My mom said after starting this gym, she had me and Yak.
Really?
This one is cooked.
Eat something too.
Don’t just listen to Yei's babbling.
If you wait until he's done, you might not get to eat anything.
Hey, you little...
Yak's got a point there.
Hey, Cher. You're my babe.
Why are you taking his side?
It's totally okay, guys.
I like listening to people.
My patients usually share their stories with me.
Come on. Don’t be so nice.
That makes me look like a bad guy here.
I didn't mean that.
You haven't eaten it.
Want me to feed you?
Open your mouth.
It's still hot.
Blow on it.
Or do you want me to do that for you too?
I can do it myself.
Dip too.
Wow.
It's delicious.
Seriously, both the pork and the dip are good.
Yei is the cook.
Wow.
It's our family’s recipe. Our mom and dad created it.
It’s so good you could open a restaurant.
Where are your mom and dad?
Let’s enjoy our food.
Have lots of pork. Yei marinated it really well.
Everyone, finish it all because pork is expensive.
Come on, eat up.
Hey, Yak. You know that your next fight is coming up, right?
Yep.
Tonight, try not to go overboard tonight with your activity.
Got it?
Yei!
This isn't the place to talk about that.
Yak.
What are you doing?
Studying?
Yes. I have a test in the morning.
Do you still need to study?
Didn’t you say you made millions from a boxing match?
This has nothing to do with boxing.
I want to graduate.
It’s someone’s dream.
Is it hard, dear?
Very hard, Mom.
No matter how much I read, I just couldn’t grasp it.
Hang in there, dear.
Study hard.
I’m waiting to have a picture with you on your graduation day.
Come on, Mom.
Let me try to make it through high school first.
My son is very talented.
I’m sure you can do it.
You flatter me too much.
My back is itchy. Can you scratch it?
Okay. Here?
No, a bit to the left.
- Right here?
- 	Yes.
You know, your mom would be really proud of you.
You think so?
Yes.
I want my mom to feel proud of me too.
Doc.
Do you think a thickhead like me can pull this off?
Without a doubt.
In the ring, you've got to read your opponent's game.
I’m sure that’s much harder than this book.
You’ve got a point.
Hey.
I learned this subject too.
Want me to tutor you?
Are you serious?
Yes.
Let this doctor teach you.
This bone is called fibula. It’s the calf bone.
Take a look at this image.
This is the bone that…
Each leg has 14 bones.
Each toe has 3 bones.
What’s wrong? Feeling itchy?
Yes. Itchy in the back.
I can’t reach the spot.
Want my help?
Can you move a bit further to the middle?
A bit lower.
Yeah.
Let’s continue.
Doc.
Hm?
Thank you.
Um.
Do your best here.
Break time?
Yes.
You were looking at Dr. Dee’s Story with his boyfriend?
Sorry, I accidentally saw your screen.
Yes, I swiped and his Story showed up.
Aren’t they lovely together?
They stay over at each other’s places.
They even post on Story to announce their relationship.
But Dr. Dee should be more cautious about his professional image.
He's too careless.
This match is in the weight class that Yoryak had to increase his weight for
in order to fight a brutal and ruthless opponent like Big Boy JC.
Let’s root for him.
Go Yoryak go!
Yoryak Phadetseuk!
Yay!!!
Yes!
You are awesome. Congrats.
I’ll prepare a special gift for you tonight.
(You are awesome. Congrats. I’ll prepare a special gift for you tonight.)
Kao, have you ever seen this?
I just learned that hundreds of thousands watch boxing matches live.
Wow.
Yak is truly incredible.
He successfully gained weight to compete in the upper weight class.
And he also managed to find time to study for his exams.
Best of all, he passed his exams too!
Dee, I think you’re really into him.
From the way he treats you,
there's a good chance he feels the same way.
What do you mean?
You two are really into each other.
You crossed the line of fake boyfriends long ago.
Kao, keep it down.
Do you want the whole hospital to know I have a fake relationship?
But your situation is a really interesting case.
What are you getting at?
The fact that you two, who pretend to be in a relationship,
look much happier than many of my patients who are in real relationships.
Me and Yak?
We look happy?
You look   happy.
Hey, Dee.
Can you do me a favor?
Sure.
What is it?
Well, I’m experimenting with something
that could benefit my patient treatments
and potentially become an additional business for me.
Woah.
That sounds like a big deal.
Do you think I can help?
You can.
Definitely can.
If being yourself makes it increasingly difficult to reveal your true feelings,
I'm curious to see if my Sleepless Sleepwear idea
can help release those suppressed feelings.
Hey!
What’s up, Big Bunny?
What’s up, Teeny Tiger?
Do you need to be this sexy being a tiger?
Brace yourself for this tiger attack.
Fierce huh?
Yak!
It feels great to get to be someone else.
Yes, Kao never disappoints me.
Kao?
Dr. Plakao, the psychiatrist?
That’s the one. He’s my one and only close friend.
What about me?
Well…
you’re not technically my close friend.
Hey.
Why are you sulking?
I’m not done yet.
You are not my close friend
but you are my super intimate close friend.
Okay?
Are we close enough now?
Um.
Enough.
If I hadn’t stumbled upon you drunk by the bus stop that night,
it would have been a shame.
Yeah.
Yak.
Since we’re in this fake relationship,
can I propose something?
What is it?
Don’t tell me…
you’re proposing that we get married.
No! That’s a bit too soon, don’t you think?
I want to take you to get a vaccination.
What vaccine?
HPV vaccine.
What?
Isn’t that for cervical cancer protection in females?
Why do I need it?
You need it.
The HPV virus is the main cause of skin infections
that can occur in the genital areas
and also there.
That means men should also get an HPV vaccine, Mr. Yoryak.
Are you worried about getting diseases via that?
I promise I’ll use this every time.
I think I should get going now.
Wait.
Do you know that thing can’t fully prevent STIs?
Just an intimate contact here…
What?
or here
can expose you to viruses.
So…
it’s the vaccine that can help protect you from viruses.
Come get the vaccine with me.
Please.
Please, please, please, please.
Enough.
I’ll go.
That’s so sweet of you, Big Doggie.
Thanks for doing it for me.
Next, Mr. Yoryak Phadetseuk, please.
Mr. Yoryak, are you here, sir?
Where are you going, Mr. Yoryak?
Mr. Yoryak, this way, sir.
Ready?
Hang in there, Yak.
It’ll be over quickly.
You are really cool, Mr. Yoryak.
Not just in boxing.
What do you mean?
Men who come to get the HPV vaccines
must care for and love their partners very much.
It’s done, sir.
Don’t forget to come for all three injections.
Okay.
Thank you for coming here to get the vaccine.
It’s not a big deal. Just a little pinch.
Doc.
You can book the next shot for me.
Now you’ve become brave.
Why? I’m a boxer.
Getting punched is more hurtful.
Surprise!
Grandma!
Hello, young man.
I’m a boxer.
So, he’s the reason you became interested in watching boxing.
If you weren’t special, he wouldn’t have given you his personal necklace.
We’re both getting closer to our goals.
Actually, you have really sweet eyes, you know?