But you said you have someone you like.
Her name is Taemrak. She’s a junior at my university.
Have you tried to win her over?
He must be really special or else you wouldn’t have given him your necklace.
What are you scheming?
I’m taking a shot with Taem as you suggested.
I think I find myself getting jealous over Yak.
Dee, you two are really into each other.
You crossed the line of fake boyfriends long ago.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, happy birthday
Make a wish, dear.
I wish for you to always have a day as wonderful as your name.
Isn’t it wonderful to have a special day like this?
It’s not hurting, not hurting.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, happy birthday
Whose birthday is it today?
Is it Namphu the strong boy's birthday?
Yes, it’s my birthday, Namphu the strong boy.
Blow out the candles.
Yeah.
We don’t have just this cake.
Bro Yoryak also has a gift for you.
Here.
Happy birthday, Namphu.
Thank you, Dr. Wandee.
Thank you, Bro Yoryak.
Wow.
How are you today?
Is the pain as bad as yesterday?
It’s much better.
I want to recover fast.
I want to go back and play with my friends at school.
How about a group power-up?
Let’s cheer for Namphu to get back to school early!
Let’s do it.
Here we go.
Power up!
Yeah!
But hold on.
How does a fighter put his guard up?
Wow.
Now show me how you punch.
Your punch is powerful.
Attaboy.
Bro Yoryak, when I grow up, I want to become a boxer like you.
Really?
Yes.
Let’s see if you’re qualified to be one.
Show me your victory pose.
Thank you very much, Doctor, Mr. Yoryak.
You’re welcome.
When I was a kid,
every time I received a present, it made me happy.
At least it reminded me I hadn't been forgotten.
Thank you.
Well, would you two mind having a picture with Namphu?
Not at all.
The gloves.
We must hold both the cake and the gloves.
Okay. Can you step closer to each other?
1, 2, 3.
Doc.
Hm?
You can remember people’s birthdays?
My seniors, juniors, professors, patients.
I can remember them all.
Let’s see…
Dr. Plakao?
Which date and month was he born?
October 1st.
And the nurses outside?
Vivi is June 15th.
Pupe is May 31st.
Did you just randomly throw out dates?
Nah. I can really remember them.
What about mine?
When’s my birthday?
Well…
Hey, hey, hey.
You can’t remember my birthday.
That’s kinda upsetting.
We’ve been together for 1 month, 5 days, and…
6 hours 32 minutes.
How come you can’t remember my birthday?
Don’t be upset.
I can remember this small detail.
You’re trying to peek at my medical profile?
No, I’m not.
I just did your physiotherapy
so I'm logging it in the patient chart.
Hey!
Don’t peek.
I didn’t.
Give me a break.
Then, when is my birthday?
Super easy.
Mr. Yoryak Phadetseuk born on December 6th.
You’re a Sagittarius.
Pretty good at peeking, Doc.
What do you mean? I didn’t peek a bit.
Anyway, I won. Now you owe me a coffee.
Hey, Doc.
Since when did I make a coffee deal with you?
Hey, Doc!
Welcome to Café for All.
Hello, Mrs. Golf.
Hello, Dr. Dee.
What can I get for you today?
My usual, please.
Sure thing.
You are Yoryak, the future world champion, right?
You watch boxing too?
Oh, I watch it for eye candy.
I mean I support all Thai boxers.
I always cheer for them.
Especially you, Yoryak.
You’re our hopeful world champion.
You have many fans, I see.
Of course.
Can I get a picture?
I want to post it on the café’s fan page.
Sure.
Dr. Wandee.
Yes?
Can you take a picture for me?
I want a picture with Yoryak.
Please.
Give me a good picture.
Make it look like we’re close.
Count for us too.
Just you two?
Yes.
Sure.
I’ll count.
1 2 3.
One more?
Yes, just in case.
Sure.
1 2 3.
Beautiful.
Thank you so much.
Can I see?
Is this good enough?
Yes.
Your cake’s ready.
What’s with the smile? It’s bugging me.
What? Why so grumpy?
Just because the café owner didn’t snap a pic of you for the page?
Not that.
She’s already posted loads of my pics there.
Really?
Yes.
Doc.
My shoulder problem won’t get worse, right?
I don’t think so.
But you should come in for physio more regularly.
Okay.
I’m running out of time before the championship fight.
You're currently ranked fifth, right?
Don't you need to work your way up to the top one by one?
Not necessarily.
When I feel confident and ready,
I can challenge opponents in any rank.
If I win, I can claim their rank.
So, you aim to dethrone the top rank	in the next fight
and become the world champion?
Of course...
not!
I'm not daring enough to challenge the top rank straight up.
I think I need one or two fights
to climb the ranks and also to earn money for the gym.
We're both getting closer to our goals.
You'll become a world champion,
and I'll secure the scholarship.
It's pretty nerve-wracking, isn't it?
Let's have a pre-celebration.
Cheers!
How was it?
The Sleepless Sleepwear.
Dr. Wandee and his boyfriend are cute together.
The pictures of them giving a gift to a young patient?
Yes.
That was a smart move.
He leverages the engagement from Yoryak’s strong fanbase.
And the concept of this movement is solid too.
A good guy who does good things for children.
It can easily win people’s hearts.
I doubt Dee thinks that deeply.
You think so?
Wow, Yoryak.
How does it make you feel when wearing?
It feels a bit strange in a good way.
What do you think, Yak?
I think if you can make the tail a bit longer,
it’ll look more realistic.
Ah, okay.
When you wear it, what score would you give it,
between 1 and 5?
5 means you really like it.
- 5 - 4.5
Wow, more than 4!
Yes!
Alright, while you are waiting for the new one,
please continue using the bunny and tiger costumes you have
and try to create a new variety of ways to enjoy them.
Confused?
I mean, don’t limit them to just one idea.
The purpose of wearing them
is to break free from any constraints.
Keep exploring.
Come here.
Find joy in becoming someone else in your own way.
Tick-tock, tick-tock, bam!
I’m outta here.
Don’t forget to think about it.
Wait, Doc!
When is your birthday?
October 1st.
Spot on!
What is this about?
Nothing.
Just a silly skepticism from someone around here.
You may go.
So?
Mr. Yoryak, born on 6th December under the sign of Sagittarius.
Hey, why the grumpy face?
Does losing bother you?
Hey!
Yak.
Is there something on my face?
Why didn’t you hold me last night?
What?
And you didn’t turn to hold me at all until morning.
Oh, come on. There’s nothing to it.
You haven’t posted any photos of us on IG.
What’s with you again?
Not even a single IG Story of us.
I rarely use IG.
I only use it to promote our gym’s classes there. You know that.
Are you seeing anyone besides me?
Have you gotten bored of me?
There.
You shook your head at me.
This is getting ridiculous, Cher.
Don’t be like this.
So are you telling me I’m acting childish?
How can I be as mature as you?
You are so far gone.
Not going to reconcile either?
What should I reconcile with you?
I don’t know what I did that upset you.
See?
You never care about me.
Cher!
Yei, get off me.
No, I won’t.
Get off me. You’re sticky.
I won’t.
Don’t be mad at me, little one.
Alright.
Now tell me what I did.
Can I say everything?
Anything you want to say.
Now tell me.
You haven’t…
gotten physical with me for days.
Just that?
Not just.
Normally, you’re not like this.
So…
do you have anyone else?
Have you gotten bored of me already?
Done talking?
Fine.
I’m done.
How many nights do I owe you?
I’ll make up for all of them.
Alright. Let’s go to our room.
And brace yourself to get physical with me.
Like this one. Okay?
Then find a nice pair of pants like this.
With this kind of shirt?
Exactly.
But they look uncomfortable and make me super sweaty.
If Mr. Yoryak wants to change his look to impress Ms. Taemrak,
he'll have to endure.
Alright.
Along with a long-sleeved shirt and pants,
you should also find a nice jacket like this one.
And then there's your hair.
You should slick it back a bit.
With just these,
you'll look sharp and clean as if you’ve stepped out of the shower.
Anything else?
Ah,
how about completing the look with a nice watch?
Whatever you think is best.
Come here.
Let me give you a reward.
Did you shop online again?
No.
I’ll go check who it is.
Surprise!
Grandma!
Hold it for me.
Where are you headed?
Inside.
Do you need to ask?
You are still very much you, my grandson.
Always been messy since young.
I’m just being consistent like you taught me.
There’s an activity with some volunteers over there today.
So I ran away.
You know that's so not my thing.
Yes, bailing out is more of your thing.
It’s great to have someone understand.
You wear size 56?
Grandma!
Come on.
Leave my stuff alone.
Just tell me where you want to go today.
I’ll keep you company.
I want to stay over a night here and spend quality time with my grandson.
Stay over?
That’s right.
We're the night owl grandma-grandson duo,
catching z's only as dawn breaks.
That’s fine.
But give me a heads up before you come over next time.
That way I can set aside my time for you
Here, you used to give me your schedule.
Let me find it.
Here. Look.
Hello, young man.
Hello.
My name is Yoryak.
Keep pulling the pants up.
Oh, you are a boxer.
Yes, I’m a boxer.
He’s the future world champion too, Grandma.
Currently, you rank…
5th.
5th in his weight class.
So, he’s the reason you became interested in watching boxing.
Wow, the food you made looks very good.
Not my cooking,
but my talent for picking the right restaurant.
You know I can’t cook.
And you stay here as Dee’s roommate?
No.
I live alone.
It’s just that…
the AC in his room is not working.
So he stays here for the time being.
That’s right.
My AC is broken.
The blade inside exploded with a loud bang.
So I asked Dee to stay here.
But you’re staying over tonight, I should go back to my room.
No, you can also stay.
The more, the merrier.
You’ve become naughtier.
You have this kind of plush toy?
No. It’s from Kao.
Yak and I are his experimental mice.
Dr. Plakao still has his quirks the same.
No, not the same.
He’s become more and more quirky over time.
That’s why he’s your friend.
Birds of a feather flock together.
It’s a shame I couldn’t see him this time.
He’s gone back to his hometown.
And what about Yoryak…
what’s the deal with him?
Well, it’s a good one.
Are you serious about him?
No.
Yak has someone already.
The relationship between me and him…
how should I call it?
Like there’s a status
but not really.
How do you feel to be in this kind of relationship?
I don’t feel anything.
The thing is, Yak and I–
We made a short-term agreement.
A very short one.
It’s so short that
I shouldn’t develop strong feelings toward him.
Stepping Over the Line
Yak!
Doc.
Why are you out here?
Checking on you.
I want to make sure you can sleep comfortably.
Very comfortable.
But I feel somewhat strange
for not having you to cuddle.
I’ve gotten used to having you in my arms.
Sure, I believe you.
Yak, what are you doing?
Grandma is here.
Just 5 minutes.
I need your power charge.
Okay.
Like this?
Yes.
Doc.
Do you think Taem will like me like you said?
Of course.
She’s going to fall for you for sure.
I can’t sleep.
Grandma!
Let’s find something fun to do.
Cheers.
Bottoms up, Grandma.
Grandma.
Yes?
May I record a video of you? You’re really cool.
You may.
But make sure to apply some filters before posting.
Noted, Mrs. Monthakarn.
Hold on.
Give me a sec, Grandma.
Here you go.
A cute accessory for the vid.
How cute.
Have a safe trip back.
I’ll find time to visit you.
Just come when you’re free.
Don’t worry about it.
I know you’re busy.
I love you the most.
I love you the most too.
Yoryak.
Help look after Dee for me.
Ah…
I will.
Goodbye.
Here.
Your grandmother is seriously cool.
Um.
Yak, do you need to go back to your gym now?
No.
Last night, Grandma stayed over at my place.
Mrs. Monthakarn is strong and healthy.
Don’t worry about her.
I regularly schedule her checkups.
I miss you, Dad, Mom.
What is it?
Don’t you think of introducing your boyfriend to your parents?
You mean fake boyfriend?
Keep it down.
You don’t want them to hear that.
Oh, please. Stop playing.
I’m not playing. I’m serious.
Dad, Mom…
I’m Yoryak, Dee’s boyfriend.
He means he’s my fake boyfriend.
Fine.
We’re going to demonstrate exercises that can make your heart stronger.
We have our special guest demonstrator, Yoryak Phadetseuk.
Hello.
Let’s get started.
Action.
Here’s the demonstration for the first exercise.
First, raise your knee to waist level.
Then swing the hand that’s opposite your raised knee.
Do this alternately, like this.
Gradually increase your speed as you go,
like this.
Cut!
What’s making you so ecstatic?
This is seriously awesome.
Abacadabra, bless me with a high score, help me get the cut.
Are you dabbling in superstition too?
Yes. Thanks for helping me with your hotness here.
What are you talking about?
That’s nonsense.
You have an excursion later this week, right?
We don’t have the tutoring session then.
Yes.
But your scores have been improving lately.
A bit, yeah.
Besides my study notes, do you have anyone else to help you?
Dr. Dee?
Yes.
That’s great. I’d like to ask for his tips too sometimes.
But this video should be okay now.
You really look so cool here.
How fortunate to know such a cool senior like you.
You’ve changed your dressing style today.
Yes, I want to try something new.
How do I look? Do you like it?
Well, you look good.
A good unfamiliar look.
So what is the excursion about?
It’s a recreational excursion held by the Student Council team.
With Ohm?
Yeah, why do you ask?
Nothing.
So there should be a lot of people joining.
The senior team staff is around 30 already.
With the addition of junior students, there are over 100 people.
That sounds like fun with a lot of people.
Send me some pics and video clips too.
If you ask for it, you’ll get tons of them.
I don’t mind..
Don’t get annoyed by the spamming later.
But let’s find something to eat now.
I exerted too much earlier from the running.
I’m starving.
Sure. Your treat, okay?
Why are you following me?
Yei,
you scared me half to death.
Don’t tell me you followed me
because you suspect I’m cheating on you?
Well, it's possible, isn't it?
I’m meeting up with some promoters
to set up fights for Yak and Jo.
Stop imagining things.
For real?
Yes.
You can come with me if you want.
Didn’t you say you didn’t like hanging around
with those tough male promoters?
I’m not going.
You can go without me.
I’m going to order stuff for our gym and head back home.
Okay.
See you later when I’m home.
Okay?
Go home safely.
Hello, bro.
I’m almost there. See you.
How’s your preparation for the scholarship going?
I’m reviewing some recent journal articles
and compiling the findings from our department's research projects
to present at the upcoming national conference
and also at the international one.
Sounds good.
What about you?
Me too, sir
I’m preparing a new research project
on sarcoma of the bone treatment in children under 13 years old.
I’m not worried about your academic aspects now.
But don’t forget to run campaigns to raise awareness and understanding
about bones and joints too.
The votes play a part in your scholarship result.
I see.
I see, sir.
I heard that Dr. Ter has actively met with numerous media reps and KOLs.
If we compare the human body to a car,
bones serve as the machinery propelling you toward your intended destination.
He also has Dr. Kwan and Nurse Noinong canvassing votes from staff
Get ready to post that on your social media.
Count on me, Dr. Kwan.
My people are ready to share it.
They could gather voters like that.
Can we really outvote them?
Wait.
Who can vote?
The hospital staff, patients, and also relatives of the patients.
I think there’s still a way.
What is it?
You just continue doing what you do, Doc.
Leave the rest to me and my friends.
What are you waiting for?
Yoryak and his folks.
They’re not here yet.
Dr. Dee.
Yes?
Give it your full power today.
We’re ready.
We can’t wait to have fun with your activity.
Got it, champ.
I’ll start it in just a minute.
Oki.
It’s all set.
Alright.
It’s time.
Let’s begin.
We’re here, Doc!
Hello, Dr. Dee.
Hello.
You guys are just in time.
Sorry. We had to pick up Taem.
When she heard about this activity, she would like to join.
Please allow me to join such a great activity like this.
No problem at all.
Shall we start?
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to My Good Day My Choice.
We all can have a good day of our choice.
It’s hard to guess who will win or lose in this competition.
Me neither.
Oh, wow.
How’s it going, Namphu?
Look.
Dr. Wandee.
Can you do storytelling?
Storytelling?
Yep.
Sure thing.
But can I have a helper?
Who?
Roarrr!!
I’m Teeny Tiger!
I’m on a quest to find the Big Bunny.
Has anyone here seen the Big Bunny?
Where is it?
Did anyone see it?
It’s over there?
Oh, there’s the Big Bunny!
Big Bunny, are you coming out of there or not?
It doesn’t want to show up. Everyone, let’s shout for it.
Big Bunny! Big Bunny! Big Bunny!
Get out of there, Big Bunny!
Big Bunny! Big Bunny!
Yeah!
Today, Teeny Tiger and Big Bunny are going to tell you a story.
It’s called "Big Bunny and Teeny Tiger."
Here we are!
What’s up, buddy?
What’s up, Big Bunny?
Kids, today we have a story to tell you.
Who wants to hear it?
Raise your hand! Raise it high!
Wow, so many of you want to hear it!
Go ahead.
You all had such great energy.
You made the patients and their families happy.
Thank you so much.
With pleasure.
We need to do this at our camp anyway.
This is like a rehearsal.
Yak, let’s put these in the car.
Yeah, let’s do it.
I’ll help.
It’s alright. I’ve got this.
Stay with Dr. Dee.
I’ll come get you when we’re done.
This too, right?
Yak told me you helped tutor him.
Ah. I used to study that subject before.
His scores improve, you know?
Fantastic.
I think it’s because of your study notes.
You cover all the key points in there.
We keep complimenting each other.
We’re still in the mood of the campaign.
My Good Day, My Choice.
Yak is fortunate to have you as his doctor.
Is that so?
Yes.
If you weren’t great, he wouldn’t have given you his personal necklace.
Taem, Phu will bring his car here.
Okay.
Alright then, I have to take off.
- See you later. - Bye.
See you too.
See ya.
Later.
Why doesn't Mr. Yoryak go celebrate with those guys?
No.
Why?
Aren’t we supposed to be together tonight?
Hey.
Don’t bail.
Not gonna.
I really won’t.
Doctor.
Thank you so much for today.
I haven’t seen Koy smile widely like this for quite some time.
I’m grateful.
And here.
I’ve got this snack for you.
Please share with him.
Their snacks are really great.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
Hey!
May I?
It’s really delicious.
Thank you again.
Enjoy it.
Please excuse me.
How could you do that in front of them?
You eat it too.
It really tastes good.
Try it.
This?
Yes.
Wow. It’s good.
Yoryak, your banana is big too.
That’s not big at all.
Come on. Put it here.
It’s not that big.
After the banana, we must add eggs, right?
Yes.
Here we go.
Oh.
What’re you doing?
Stop it.
You're using too much force.
The egg is all over your palm.
I couldn’t grab it properly.
I don’t get why you suddenly feel like baking.
Aren’t you exhausted enough from today?
The activity today makes me think of my grandma.
I want to bake this and give it to her.
So this is for Mrs. Monthakarn, my idol?
Okidoki.
I’ll do my best.
Dee, you just stand there and do nothing.
Leave it all to me.
You are so extra.
Why do we have to make it hard before eating this?
Isn’t it common?
If you want to eat good stuff,
you must learn to wait.
But I can eat you without having to wait.
Hey, what nonsense are you speaking?
Focus on it.
Gotcha!
Oh, do you want to be baked in the oven too?
How cute.
No, Yak!
Yak!
You did so great today.
Not that great.
But I’m thankful for your help.
I’m on your team.
Thanks for bringing me here and treating me to this meal.
This place is really nice.
The food looks good too.
Do you know about this place from someone?
Ah, I found it from an internet review.
Ah.
Let's start eating.
What are you listening to? Can I hear it too?
Don't make me overstep any further
One look into your eyes and my stomach flutters
Stop before my heart falls any deeper
Ooh baby, I don’t know how to stop myself either
Then don't make me overstep any further
One look into your eyes and my stomach flutters
Stop before my heart falls any deeper
Ooh baby…
Hey, tiny dude, want to drink with us?
His name is Gooddy.
Ah.
What’s up, Gooddy?
Thank you, Yak, for today.
It should be me who says that.
You invited me to do a good thing.
Ouch.
What happened?
Got dust in your eye?
I guess.
Let me see.
What?
Actually, you have really sweet eyes, you know?
Then don't make me overstep any further
The cake should be ready. Let me go check it.
One look into your eyes and my stomach flutters
Stop before my heart falls any deeper
Ooh baby, I don’t know how to stop myself either
Then don't make me overstep any further
One look into your eyes and my stomach flutters
Stop before my heart falls any deeper
(#GOODDY is kinda cute <3)
Ooh baby, I don’t know how to stop myself either
(kinda cute #GOODDY)
Those are the toothbrushes you give to your young patients.
Yes.
They are cute.
I want to use them too.
Good. They are really cute.
Well then, mine is the left one, yours is the right one.
Why so?
It must be YoryakWandee.
Not WantdeeYoryak, right?
Why? Why can’t it be that?
Come here and brush your teeth.
Is that correct?
Yes.
No, it must be this.
Come on, Doc.
The first letter of my name comes before yours.
That's the Thai alphabetical order.
No.
Stop.
WandeeYoryak.
YoryakWandee.
Hey, Yak! No.
Enough talk.
Yak, let’s go hang out together and just be ourselves.
I love you, Dee.
I think Dr. Ter realizes how he feels about you.
Let him. I don’t care.
You must choose now who exactly you have feelings for.